[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1978 movie Halloween is set in the real town of Haddonfield, NJ.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1999 film from this quote: It doesnt surprise me that theres another woman. Of course, the fact that shes dead gives one pause.", "correct_answer": "Stir of Echoes", "incorrect_answers": ["Nightwatch", "The Haunting", "The Craft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many pounds of leaves can a giraffe consume daily?", "correct_answer": "140 pounds", "incorrect_answers": ["60 pounds", "100 pounds", "210 pounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name for the rose species Rosa Chinensis?", "correct_answer": "China rose", "incorrect_answers": ["Cabbage rose", "Blood rose", "Black rose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Scarface, Tonys sister marries Tonys best friend behind Tonys back.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of organisms cause the parasitic infection known as ringworm?", "correct_answer": "Fungi", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Mites", "Intestinal worms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What U.S. National Park saw a large and very destructive fire in 1988?", "correct_answer": "Yellowstone", "incorrect_answers": ["Death Valley", "Sequoia", "Yosemite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The surface of this planet is unique, it is the only one which has water in large quantities.", "correct_answer": "Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturn", "Pluto", "Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the name under which Opel designs are sold in the UK?", "correct_answer": "Vauxhall", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturn", "Holden", "Chevrolet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city is the capital of the Kingdom of Morocco.", "correct_answer": "Rabat", "incorrect_answers": ["Suva", "Yaounde", "Tehran"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mississippi is the longest North American river. The Missouri is the second. What is the third longest?", "correct_answer": "Rio Grande", "incorrect_answers": ["Arkansas", "Colorado", "Hudson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what car does James Bond chase the villains henchwoman in A View to a Kill?", "correct_answer": "Mercedes", "incorrect_answers": ["Volvo", "Rover", "Peugeot"]}]